The answer to the first question is that the XML element name is here, TextView.
Ответ на первый вопрос о названии элемента XML, вот здесь - TextView.
It follows the open angle bracket.
После открывающей угловой скобки.
Then, all the attributes are below the XML element name, and
После, все аттрибуты идут после названия элемента XML и
I've underlined the attribute names here.
подчеркнула здесь названия аттрибутов.
They're on the left hand side of the equal sign.
Они все стоят слева от знака равенства.
They include android:text, android:textColor, and so on.
Это android:text, android:textColor, и так далее.
If you put the attribute values, like Happy Birthday or the color/white or
Если укажете значения аттрибутов - Happy Birthday или color/white
black, that's incorrect, because those are the attribute values, and
то это неправильно, потому что это значения аттрибутов а
it's asking for the names.
вопрос был о названиях.
The last question is, on what line number is a tag closed?
Последний вопрос - в какой строке стоит закрывающая метка?
Then we see the forward slash and
Вот мы видим прямой слеш и
the closing angle bracket on the last line, which is line 6.
закрывающую угловую скобку в последней строке, то есть в строке 6.
This means that it's a self-closing tag,
Это самозакрывающаяся метка,
because we open the text view tag here and then we close it right away.
мы открыли метку здесь, а здесь ее закрыли.